terababes.com 2007-12-10

# TeraBabes - Privacy Policy

TeraBabes.com has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.  The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for TeraBabes.com.

**Web Site Log Files**

TeraBabes.com analyzes traffic to this web site, but does not create individual profiles for each visitor.

**Cookies**

TeraBabes.com does not use internet "cookies" on our web site.

TeraBabes.com uses outside ad companies to display ads on our site.  These ads may contain cookies.  Any cookies received with banner ads are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

**Mailing Lists**

TeraBabes.com maintains a subscription Email List.  All users must confirm their subscriptions via return email.  Users are never added based on requesting information, making a purchase, or forgetting to uncheck some box during ordering.  Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time by simply unsubscribing.

**Contests**

TeraBabes.com runs contests where we ask visitors for contact information (specifically, email address).  Contact information from the contests is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary (if they win).  Specific contest rules and regulations can be found on the Contests page, and rules may vary from contest to contest depending on Sponsor and respective guidelines.

**Information Collection and Use**

With the exception of recording your email address if you sign up for our Email List, as described above, this Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We will not sell or give your name, email address, or any other personal information to any outside party, nor will we use any of your personal information for any purposes other than as described in this Privacy Policy.  TeraBabes.com is dedicated to maintaining your privacy.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

This site contains links to other sites.  TeraBabes.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

TeraBabes.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of TeraBabes.com, or your dealings with TeraBabes.com, please  contact us.
